Everyone has a secret.
Plainclothes is a drama, romance, crime film directed by Carmen Emmi.
In 1990s New York, an undercover police officer receives
an assignment to lure and arrest gay men.
However, he's surprised to discover a scintillating
connection with one of his targets.
As their secret connection deepens and internal pressure to deliver arrests
intensifies, he finds himself torn between duty and desire.
Lucas, played by Tom Blyth.
Andrew, played by Russell Tovey.
Emily, played by Amy Forsyth.
Marie, played by Maria Dizzia.
Ron, played by Christian Cooke.
Uncle Paul, played by Gabe Fazio.
Plainclothes is a 2025 romantic thriller drama film directed by Carmen Emmi and starring Tom Blyth,
Russell Tovey, Maria Dizzia, Christian Cooke, Gabe Fazio, Amy Forsyth, and John Bedford Lloyd.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 26,
2025, and was released in the United States on September 19, 2025.
The film explores themes of entrapment, ex-girlfriend,
based on true story, death of father, grief.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.